I love this it reminds me of Lasik you
know basic did you have Lasik I I have
not have Lasik have you I gotta wait a
few years they say I gotta wait till I
am 80.
wait a minute that was uh
Atarax yeah
[Music]
what's up Grandma hey papa I'm going to
teach you something what something very
history I don't want to do an enema
again that thing was ridiculous I'm not
going to show you an anime although you
really needed it yes so I'm going to
teach you something take this piece of
paper we're gonna try this I'm gonna you
know you already folded it on that
diagonal
and this is called a mountain fold you
know why it's called a mountain fold
because it's impossible to get over and
no one wants to do it
so now we do we do a valley fold on the
this is where you put the coke
what you think if that's yours if you do
this here like this
then you do now you take the end
take the dance of the diagonal and Tuck
these in so you make a square
so what happened to you do this how did
you screw this up I don't know
[Music]
oh yes
now for an origamis if you look at a
piece of paper I know what you did if I
look at this I know that it's a crane
really yes I can okay yes I know well
that's good
it's good for me
well the close enough
it looks like the hats that British
people wear on Christmas man this is
really addictive oh you made so many
what is that it's a
stork here's a crab cute this is a swan
now this is a traditional Chinese the
very first that my mother ever made for
me was this boat looks like a nice
little that's a nice boat yeah do you
want to see what I made yeah all right
check out this
it's from memory NASA NASA it looks like
a a shooting uh a spaceship Runway
Runway Runway and then here are the
wings where people will sit okay yeah I
made another one too
yeah this one is an elephant
okay it looks like I have it looks more
like a I know there is still spaceship
aspects of this yeah but I figure I
think I think I went too long on the
trunk oh yeah well the trunk is longer
this one is a middle finger to the man
middle finger middle finger to the menu
for one of these two things on the side
then your other your knuckles your
knuckles yeah you can't have a hand
without a knuckle this one this one
actually this one is interesting this
one is a
garden snake it looks like a
balls
thank you so much for this time Grandma
very welcome you are very creative so I
can make you a thousand elephants and I
could string them up and put them all in
your room that would be my message of
love for you um little LED lights in
them as well okay we could do that look
that's good look bad
yeah peace sign yeah what it is what it
is what it is yeah yeah what it is